barnonedrinks.com 2006-06-13

# Learn more about Bar None!

**_Bar-None Info_**  
  
 [Credits | **Legal** | Links | Site Info ] 

## Privacy Statement

### Introduction

P.S. Productions has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Bar-None Drink Recipes. In general it states that, except in the case of contests where you explicitly give us permission to provide your contact information to contest sponsors, your personal information will only be known to two parties: yourself and P.S. Productions.

### General Information

We use the information provided by your web browser (your IP address, the last site that referred you to us, and your browser version) to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and in the case of our user forums to track abusive users. We may also use cookies to store your site navigation preferences (e.g. measurement system, background colour, forum username and email).

### Site Configuration

Our site configuration form requests that users give us contact information (like their name and email address). This is optional and is used to subscribe users to the mailing lists that they have requested and to set their default username and address for use in the forums. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out/change section below.

### Online Surveys

Our online surveys may ask visitors for demographic information (like their age or gender). This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis only (i.e. your personal information can not be identified as belonging to you) in order to allow us to better sell the advertising that keeps our site online. 

### Contests

From time to time we run contests on our site in which we may ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their age or gender). In some cases, in order for us to provide prizes for the contests on our site, we are obligated to give a list of the entrant information to the providers of those prizes. If you do not wish to have your information distributed, you may choose not to enter the contests.

### Public Forums

This site makes forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Third Party Advertising

We use MaxWorldwide, BUDS INC and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php) or [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

### Opt-Out/Update

Our site generally provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. The only exception to this is contests, where the list of entrants is given to the providers of the prizes. The user may opt not to enter the contest if they do not want their addresses distributed.

This site also gives users the option of changing and modifying information previously provided.

You can change your existing information in our database or choose to be removed from any or all further contact by sending us email at the address at the bottom of this page. In the near future, this will also be available from our user config page. 

### Disclaimer

Once information that a user has authorized us to provide to a third party has left our control, we can not be held responsible for removing that information from the third party's database.

This site contains links to other sites. **Bar-None Drink Recipes** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

> Bar-None Drink Recipes 2598A Rosstown Road Nanaimo, B.C. Canada V9T 3S1
